Guide to the Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South Records, 1940-1997 and undated, bulk 1993-1997 RL.00170
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Printed Materials Series (PM), ca. 1940-1997 (bulk 1993-1997) [RESTRICTED], 9 boxes
  - Charlotte, N.C. and Environs
    - Davis, Samuel (Box PM2)
    - DeLaine, Joseph (Box PM2)
    - Donald, Morris (Box PM2)
    - Elder, Thereasea (Box PM2)
    - Ely, Vermelle (Box PM2)
    - Ferguson, Charles (Box PM2)
    - Goins, Harry (Box PM2)
    - Goins, Sudie (Box PM2)
    - Golden, Willie (Box PM2)
    - Goodwin, Florence (Box PM2)
    - Graham, Estelle (Box PM2)
    - Hagans, Zenobia (Box PM2)
    - Hart, Alice (Box PM2)
    - Hayes, Dorothy (Box PM2)
    - Heath, Henry (Box PM2)
    - Holmes, Walter (Box PM2)
    - Hunter, Annie (Box PM2)
    - Hunter, Wright (Box PM2)
    - Jones, Cedric (Box PM2)
    - Jones, Charles (Box PM2)
    - Jones, Ione (Box PM2)
    - Leak, Doretha (Box PM2)
    - Lynch, Kathleen (Box PM2)
    - McClain, Marilyn (Box PM2)
    - McClain, Wyonella (Box PM2)
    - McCorkle, Alene (Box PM2)
    - McDuffie, Jean (Box PM2)
    - McKee, Minnie (Box PM2)
    - Miller, Bernice (Box PM2)
    - Miller, Larry (Box PM2)
    - Morris, Ruth (Box PM2)
    - Mungo, Alma (Box PM2)
    - Neal, Margaret (Box PM2)
    - Neal, Sephus (Box PM2)
    - Oxner, Nell (Box PM2)
    - Randolph, Elizabeth (Box PM2)
    - Rann, Emery (Box PM2)
    - Ray, Clyde (Box PM2)
    - Robinson, Violet (Box PM2)
    - Sammons, Lena (Box PM2)
    - Shipman, Mamie (Box PM2)
    - Shute, Amanda (Box PM2)
    - Shute, Mathew, Sr. (Box PM2)
    - Sigler, Lloyd (Box PM2)
    - Simmons, Curtina (Box PM2)
    - Spears, Alphatene (Box PM2)
    - Spears, Rufus, Sr. (Box PM2)
    - Steele, Dorothy (Box PM2)
    - Stovall, Lille (Box PM2)
    - Strong, Clyde (Box PM2)
    - Stroud, Daisy (Box PM2)
    - Stroud, Gerson (Box PM2)
    - Stroud, Wirron (Box PM2)
    - Swift, Beatrice (Box PM2)
    - Taylor, Mildred (Box PM2)
    - Taylor, Rosita (Box PM2)
    - Thompson, Jean (Box PM2)
    - Thornton, Anita (Box PM2)
    - Twitty, Walter (Box PM2)
    - Weathers, Maxine (Box PM2)
    - White, Allegray (Box PM2)
    - Williams, Margaret (Box PM2)
    - Williams, Tommy (Box PM2)
    - Wilson, Catherine (Box PM2)
    - Woods, Effie (Box PM2)
    - Woods, Clifton, Jr. (Box PM2)
    - Wyche, Grace (Box PM2)
    - Wyche, Thomas (Box PM2)
    - Wynn, Maria (Box PM2)
    - Yongue, Imogene (Box PM2)
    - Yongue, William, Jr. (Box PM2)
  - Durham, N.C. and Environs (Box PM3)
    - Atwater, Ann (Box PM3)
    - Blue, Ila (Box PM3)
    - Blunt, Russell (Box PM3)
    - Brinkley, Harriette (Box PM3)
    - Brodie, Arthur (Box PM3)
    - Bryant, Artelia (Box PM3)
    - Bryant, R. (Box PM3)
    - Butterfield, George (Box PM3)
    - Bynum, Ernestine (Box PM3)
    - Cherry, Willie (Box PM3)
    - Clement, William (Box PM3)
    - Crockett, Manuel (Box PM3)
    - Davis, Willie, Jr. (Box PM3)
    - Duncan, Anne (Box PM3)
    - Edmonds, Vivian (Box PM3)
    - Fitts, Howard, Jr. (Box PM3)
    - Garrett, York (Box PM3)
    - Hinton, Collins (Box PM3)
    - Hughley, Sadie (Box PM3)
    - Knight, Christopher (Box PM3)
    - Lee, James (Box PM3)
    - Livingston, Omeda (Box PM3)
    - Lucas, Julia (Box PM3)
    - Lyons, Theresa (Box PM3)
    - Malone, Calvin (Box PM3)
    - McCandies, Emily (Box PM3)
    - McCoy, Vivian (Box PM3)
    - McCullers, Henderson (Box PM3)
    - McCullers, Patricia (Box PM3)
    - Mimms, Horace (Box PM3)
    - Moore, III, Malvin (Box PM3)
    - Owens, Sam (Box PM3)
    - Page, Benjamin (Box PM3)
    - Page, Mildred (Box PM3)
    - Quigless, Milton (Box PM3)
    - Rivera, Alexander (Box PM3)
    - Sanders, Easter (Box PM3)
    - Sanders, James (Box PM3)
    - Scarborough, George (Box PM3)
    - Tapp, Peggy (Box PM3)
    - Taylor, Jennie (Box PM3)
    - West End Oral History Project (Box PM3)
    - White, Clarence (Box PM3)
    - White, Nathaniel (Box PM3)
    - Wilson, Sandra (Box PM3)
  - Enfield, N.C. and Environs
    - Allen, Suzie (Box PM3)
    - Artis, Betty (Box PM3)
    - Babcock, Annie (Box PM3)
    - Battle, James (Box PM3)
    - Bodie, Mary (Box PM3)
    - Boone, Dorothy (Box PM3)
    - Boone, Erma (Box PM3)
    - Brantley, Leroy (Box PM3)
    - Bricks Club (Box PM3)
    - Brinkley, Claudia (Box PM3)
    - Brinkley, Richard (Box PM3)
    - Bronson, Bernice (Box PM3)
    - Bullock, Lester (Box PM3)
    - Cannon, Dorothy (Box PM3)
    - Cochran, Doris (Box PM3)
    - Cochran, Salter (Box PM3)
    - Cofield, Mae (Box PM3)
    - Coley, Frederick (Box PM3)
    - Crowell, Maggie (Box PM3)
    - Daniel, Mayonie (Box PM3)
    - Edge, Effie (Box PM3)
    - Edge, Richard (Box PM3)
    - Ellis, Margaret (Box PM3)
    - Exum, Julia (Box PM3)
    - Farmer, Anthony (Box PM3)
    - Farmer, Bertha (Box PM3)
    - Fenner, Lillie (Box PM3)
    - Foreman, Annie (Box PM3)
    - Forney, Myrtle (Box PM3)
    - Francis, Eddie (Box PM3)
    - Francis, Eddie, Jr. (Box PM3)
    - Francis, Eullia (Box PM3)
    - Grant, Florenza (Box PM3)
    - Grant, Gary (Box PM3)
    - Grant, Matthew (Box PM3)
    - Grant, Richard (Box PM3)
    - Harvey, Theresa (Box PM3)
    - Hedgepath, Clarence (Box PM3)
    - Hinton, Katherine (Box PM3)
    - Hunter, Nancy (Box PM3)
    - Johnson, Beaulah (Box PM3)
    - Johnson, Lucille (Box PM3)
    - Johnson, Ruth (Box PM3)
    - Johnson, Jack William (Box PM3)
    - Kea, Gladys (Box PM3)
    - Lee, Katherine (Box PM3)
    - Lee, Richard (Box PM3)
    - Leonard, Walter (Box PM3)
    - Lowe, Daisy (Box PM3)
    - Lowe, Willie (Box PM3)
    - Lynch, Georgia (Box PM3)
    - Lynch, Orator (Box PM3)
    - Lyon, David (Box PM3)
    - Lyons, Celestine (Box PM3)
    - Mallary, Lillian (Box PM3)
    - Mallory, Dezell (Box PM3)
    - Mann, Effie (Box PM3)
    - Marable, Azree (Box PM3)
    - McWilliams, Ada (Box PM3)
    - Moore, Fred (Box PM3)
    - Moore, Mildred (Box PM3)
    - Morrow, Katherine (Box PM3)
    - Pearce, Mildred (Box PM3)
    - Pelerson, Deatherine (Box PM3)
    - Pittman, Emerson (Box PM3)
    - Plummer, Vera (Box PM3)
    - Powell, Clarence (Box PM3)
    - Powell, Cocolua (Box PM3)
    - Powell, Willie (Box PM3)
    - Reynolds, Pam (Box PM3)
    - Rogers, Mary (Box PM3)
    - Ruel, Solomon (Box PM3)
    - Russel, Elvenia (Box PM3)
    - Scott, Jasper (Box PM3)
    - Scott, Louise (Box PM3)
    - Smith, Cassie (Box PM3)
    - Smith, Lillie (Box PM3)
    - Spence, Vivian (Box PM3)
    - Thompson, Addie (Box PM3)
    - Thorne, Annie (Box PM3)
    - Tillery, Roy (Box PM3)
    - Tillery Community Center (Box PM3)
    - Valentine, Gracie (Box PM3)
    - Ward, Willie (Box PM3)
    - Weathersbee, Susie (Box PM3)
    - Whitaker, Mildred (Box PM3)
    - Whitehead, Lossie (Box PM3)
    - Wilkens, Evelyn (Box PM3)
    - Williams, Lola (Box PM3)
    - Wills, Almyra (Box PM3)
    - Wills, Hubert (Box PM3)
  - James City Historical Society
    - Boyd, Aaron (Box PM3)
    - Clemmons, Ernestine (Box PM3)
    - Gavin, Annie (Box PM3)
    - Pleasant Hill (Box PM3)
    - Spivey, Bill (Box PM3)
    - Spivey, Dorothy (Box PM3)
  - LeFlore Co., Miss. and Environs
    - Alexander, Essie (Box PM3)
    - Allen, Lou (Box PM3)
    - Automon, Sarah (Box PM3)
    - Bailey, George (Box PM3)
    - Barber, Corean (Box PM3)
    - Bays, Georgia (Box PM3)
    - Bowie, Eura (Box PM3)
    - Brown, Jackson (Box PM3)
    - Bynum, Rosie (Box PM3)
    - Carthan, Eddie (Box PM3)
    - Clayborn, Arthur, Jr. (Box PM3)
    - Conley, Annie (Box PM3)
    - Davis, Arnette (Box PM3)
    - Davis, William (Box PM3)
    - Ewing, Alice (Box PM3)
    - Federick, Booker (Box PM3)
    - Flemming, Cora (Box PM3)
    - Gibson, O. (Box PM3)
    - Giles, Alice (Box PM3)
    - Green, Ara (Box PM3)
    - Gulledge, Lucinda (Box PM3)
    - Hammond, Sadie (Box PM3)
    - Howard, Irene (Box PM3)
    - Ingram, James (Box PM3)
    - Jackson, Ruthie (Box PM3)
    - Johnson, John (Box PM3)
    - Johnson, Mandie (Box PM3)
    - Jones, Johnny (Box PM3)
    - Lacy, Frank (Box PM3)
    - Leach, Herman (Box PM3)
    - Lindsey, Robert (Box PM3)
    - Livingston, Daisy (Box PM3)
    - Love, Hettie (Box PM3)
    - Lucas, Maurice (Box PM3)
    - Malone, Ruth (Box PM3)
    - Martin, Virginia (Box PM3)
    - Matthews, David (Box PM3)
    - Matthews, John (Box PM3)
    - McCaskill, Willie (Box PM3)
    - McDonald, Nathan (Box PM3)
    - Moore, Georgia (Box PM3)
    - Payne, Bertha (Box PM4)
    - Payne, Jessie, Jr. (Box PM4)
    - Peyton, A. (Box PM4)
    - Pitts, Elizabeth (Box PM4)
    - Reed, Willie (Box PM4)
    - Robinson, Cathon (Box PM4)
    - Robinson, James (Box PM4)
    - Robinson, Juvernia (Box PM4)
    - Rolling, Susie (Box PM4)
    - Rose, Richard (Box PM4)
    - Russell, Erma (Box PM4)
    - Sanders, Rosie (Box PM4)
    - Scott, Charles (Box PM4)
    - Scott, H. (Box PM4)
    - Sculark, Walter (Box PM4)
    - Simmons, Hattie (Box PM4)
    - Simms, Ruth (Box PM4)
    - Sims, Maggie (Box PM4)
    - Stewart, Jessie (Box PM4)
    - Stewart, Lillie (Box PM4)
    - Stewart, William (Box PM4)
    - Taylor, Julia (Box PM4)
    - Taylor, Laura (Box PM4)
    - Taylor, Lola (Box PM4)
    - Ward, Alma (Box PM4)
    - Washington, Genora (Box PM4)
    - Washington, Willie (Box PM4)
    - Weston, Minnie (Box PM4)
    - White, Bernice (Box PM4)
    - White, Dorsey (Box PM4)
    - Wicks, David (Box PM4)
    - Williams, H. (Box PM4)
    - Williams, R. (Box PM4)
    - Williams, Ruby (Box PM4)
    - Young, Chris, Sr. (Box PM4)
  - Memphis, Tenn. and Environs
    - Ateman, Ada (Box PM4)
    - Ballard, Lozell (Box PM4)
    - Bates, Evelyn (Box PM4)
    - Bond, Noah (Box PM4)
    - Bond, Noah [et. al.] (Box PM4)
    - Boyd, LeRoy (Box PM4)
    - Bradley, James (Box PM4)
    - Bragg, Savy (Box PM4)
    - Branch, Lanetha (Box PM4)
    - Brandon, Grace (Box PM4)
    - Broome, Willie (Box PM4)
    - Brown, Allen, Jr. (Box PM4)
    - Brown, Lillie (Box PM4)
    - Bryant, Susie (Box PM4)
    - Buggs, Dorothy (Box PM4)
    - Butler, Willie (Box PM4)
    - Chalmers, Artherene (Box PM4)
    - Conley, Oatie (Box PM4)
    - Cooper, Barbara (Box PM4)
    - Cooper, John (Box PM4)
    - Crivens, Hortense (Box PM4)
    - Cross, Blondale (Box PM4)
    - Cummings, Mattie (Box PM4)
    - Davis, Essie (Box PM4)
    - Davis, Matthew (Box PM4)
    - Edmond, Margarette (Box PM4)
    - Edwards, Mack (Box PM4)
    - Farris, Elizabeth (Box PM4)
    - Fitzgerald, Mae (Box PM4)
    - Forest, Earl (Box PM4)
    - Fort, Marie (Box PM4)
    - Gilliland, Jessie (Box PM4)
    - Gladney, Martha (Box PM4)
    - Golden, Addie (Box PM4)
    - Griffin, Lovie (Box PM4)
    - Harrell, Willie (Box PM4)
    - Hill, Lutisha (Box PM4)
    - Hunt, Edgar (Box PM4)
    - Hunt, Euless (Box PM4)
    - Jenkins, Henrene (Box PM4)
    - Johnson, Agnes (Box PM4)
    - Johnson, Elnora (Box PM4)
    - Johnson, Harry (Box PM4)
    - Johnson, Helen (Box PM4)
    - Johnson, JoAnn (Box PM4)
    - Johnson, Ralph (Box PM4)
    - Jones, Amy (Box PM4)
    - Jones, Andrenetta (Box PM4)
    - Jones, Charles (Box PM4)
    - Jones, Johnny (Box PM4)
    - Jones, Merlin (Box PM4)
    - Jones, Otha B. Strong (Box PM4)
    - Jordan, John (Box PM4)
    - Kirkon, Lillie (Box PM4)
    - Lampkins, Roosevelt (Box PM4)
    - Laws, Irene (Box PM4)
    - Lawson, Mary (Box PM4)
    - Leachman, Ida (Box PM4)
    - Lee, Alversa (Box PM4)
    - Lewis, Charles (Box PM4)
    - Lewis, Charles [et. al.] (Box PM4)
    - Lewis, Lenora (Box PM4)
    - Lewis, Lucille (Box PM4)
    - Lindsey, James (Box PM4)
    - Malden, Rosa (Box PM4)
    - Mayweather, Hortense (Box PM4)
    - McDowell, Earline (Box PM4)
    - McGee, Hazel (Box PM4)
    - McGhee, Hazel (Box PM4)
    - McKinley, Lucille (Box PM4)
    - McKinley, Melvina (Box PM4)
    - McKinley, Rebecca (Box PM4)
    - McKinney, Frederick (Box PM4)
    - McNeal, Mary (Box PM4)
    - Morris, Alma (Box PM4)
    - Murphy, Margarette (Box PM4)
    - Neyland, Jerry (Box PM4)
    - Ordley, Carrie (Box PM4)
    - Pearson, Frank (Box PM4)
    - Peterson, Ida (Box PM4)
    - Rayburn, Lafayette (Box PM4)
    - Richmond, Benjamin (Box PM4)
    - Robinson, Mary (Box PM4)
    - Rodgers, Annie (Box PM4)
    - Rogers, Taylor (Box PM4)
    - Scott, Joseph (Box PM4)
    - Simons, Harry (Box PM4)
    - Sims, Bertha (Box PM4)
    - Sims, Constant (Box PM4)
    - Sims, Melma (Box PM4)
    - Smith, Georgia Maxine (Box PM4)
    - Spencer, Robert (Box PM4)
    - Starling, Evelyn (Box PM4)
    - Taylor, Edmonia (Box PM4)
    - Taylor, Evelyn (Box PM4)
    - Thompson, Ralph (Box PM4)
    - Tucker, Callie (Box PM4)
    - Turner, Allegra (Box PM4)
    - Turner, Elaine (Box PM4)
    - Turner, Johnnie (Box PM4)
    - Turner, Sally (Box PM4)
    - Veazy, Rodie (Box PM4)
    - Walton, Jessie (Box PM4)
    - Ware, Elizabeth (Box PM4)
    - Westbrook, Dorothy (Box PM4)
    - Whitehead, Earline (Box PM4)
    - Williams, Alvia (Box PM4)
    - Williams, Elijah (Box PM4)
    - Williams, Percy (Box PM4)
    - Wilson, Emogene (Box PM4)
    - Withers, Ernest (Box PM4)
    - Woods, Earnest (Box PM4)
    - Yahweh, Abdul (Box PM4)
  - Mid-Michigan
    - Birden, Charles, Sr. (Box PM4)
  - Muhlenberg Co., Ky. and Environs
    - Cartwright, Mabel (Box PM4)
    - Dulin, Mary (Box PM4)
    - Eaves, Elcie (Box PM4)
    - Eaves, James (Box PM4)
    - Ellis, Wilodean (Box PM4)
    - Gilmore, Sydney, Jr. (Box PM4)
    - Goins, Mallie (Box PM4)
    - Harris, Carrie (Box PM4)
    - Horton, Aldrich (Box PM4)
    - Lovan, Al (Box PM4)
    - Martin, Dorothy (Box PM4)
    - McClellan, Arthur (Box PM4)
    - Smith, Leslie (Box PM4)
    - Stafford, Carrie (Box PM4)
    - Stafford, Willie (Box PM4)
      (This box also includes Alexander X. Byrd's research notebook)
  - New Bern, N.C. and Environs (Box PM5)
    - Adams, Eva (Box PM5)
    - Attmore, Arlestus (Box PM5)
    - Barrett, Mamie (Box PM5)
    - Becton-Fleming, Velma (Box PM5)
    - Best, Hayward (Box PM5)
    - Best, Stephen (Box PM5)
    - Bland, Carolyn (Box PM5)
    - Bland, James (Box PM5)
    - Booker, Wallace (Box PM5)
    - Boyd, Aaron (Box PM5)
    - Brown, Alfreda (Box PM5)
    - Bryan, Dorothy (Box PM5)
    - Bryan, Samuel (Box PM5)
    - Bryant, Arabelle (Box PM5)
    - Campbell, Emeler (Box PM5)
    - Campbell, Sarah (Box PM5)
    - Carter, Dorcas (Box PM5)
    - Clemmons, Ernestine (Box PM5)
    - Collins, Alfreda (Box PM5)
    - Daniels, Dolletha (Box PM5)
    - Davis, Rebecca (Box PM5)
    - Dent, Mary (Box PM5)
    - Dillahunt, Leamon (Box PM5)
    - Donaldson, Annie (Box PM5)
    - Donlap, Nettie (Box PM5)
    - Downing, Myrtle (Box PM5)
    - Dudley, Lucy (Box PM5)
    - Dunson, Helen (Box PM5)
    - Evans, Narcissus (Box PM5)
    - Forbes, Rowene (Box PM5)
    - Franklin, William (Box PM5)
    - Gavin, Annie (Box PM5)
    - George, Grace (Box PM5)
    - Gramtham, Rosa (Box PM5)
    - Harding, James (Box PM5)
    - Harris, Clayton (Box PM5)
    - Hayes, James (Box PM5)
    - Hickman, Willie (Box PM5)
    - Jones, Frances (Box PM5)
    - Joyner, Luvenia (Box PM5)
    - Kelsey, Christine (Box PM5)
    - League, Mary (Box PM5)
    - Lewis, Astor (Box PM5)
    - Lewis, James (Box PM5)
    - Lewis, Marion (Box PM5)
    - Lewis, Rosetta (Box PM5)
    - Lewis, Ruth (Box PM5)
    - McCoy, Lucinda (Box PM5)
    - Moore, Catherine (Box PM5)
    - Moore, George (Box PM5)
    - Morgan, Leander (Box PM5)
    - Moye, John (Box PM5)
    - Payne, Velma (Box PM5)
    - Perry, Mary (Box PM5)
    - Pickens, Lucille (Box PM5)
    - Roberts, Mary (Box PM5)
    - Ryder, Loretta (Box PM5)
    - Ryder, Naomi (Box PM5)
    - Simmons, Ruth (Box PM5)
    - Spicer, Bessie (Box PM5)
    - Stone, Mary (Box PM5)
    - Strong, Andrew (Box PM5)
    - Sutton, Georgia (Box PM5)
    - Wade, Harriet (Box PM5)
    - White, Clay (Box PM5)
    - White, Mary (Box PM5)
    - White, Ronald (Box PM5)
    - Whitfield, Emma (Box PM5)
    - Williams, Janie (Box PM5)
    - Wordlaw, Clarita (Box PM5)
  - New Iberia, La. and Environs
    - Allen, JoAnn (Box PM5)
    - Auguster, Edran (Box PM5)
    - Bernard, Lucille (Box PM5)
    - Bijou, Hattie (Box PM5)
    - Bijou, Prosper (Box PM5)
    - Blaise, Edward (Box PM5)
    - Bonds, Edward (Box PM5)
    - Boutte, Lester (Box PM5)
    - Broussard,Anderson (Box PM5)
    - Carson, Martha (Box PM5)
    - Chassion, Jessie (Box PM5)
    - Cobb, Doris (Box PM5)
    - Coleman, Baron (Box PM5)
    - Crofton, Clarence (Box PM5)
    - Drexler, Clarence (Box PM5)
    - Drexler, Ruby (Box PM5)
    - Durall, Melvenia (Box PM5)
    - Gabriel, Audrey (Box PM5)
    - Gibson, Cora (Box PM5)
    - Gibson, Ivory (Box PM5)
    - Granger, Joseph (Box PM5)
    - Hadnott, Frances (Box PM5)
    - Hadnott, Louie (Box PM5)
    - Harding, William (Box PM5)
    - Henderson, John (Box PM5)
    - Henderson, James, Sr. (Box PM5)
    - Henry, Joseph (Box PM5)
    - Hills, Erline (Box PM5)
    - Jack, Georgiana (Box PM5)
    - Jackson, Cora (Box PM5)
    - Jackson, Cyrus (Box PM5)
    - James, Herman (Box PM5)
    - Jean-Batiste, Maude (Box PM5)
    - Jones, Josephine (Box PM5)
    - Jones, Mertha (Box PM5)
    - Jones, Mertha (Box PM5)
    - Joseph, Arthur (Box PM5)
    - Joseph, Rose (Box PM5)
    - Knatt, Alvin (Box PM5)
    - Knatt, Clement (Box PM5)
    - Knatt, Foreman (Box PM5)
    - Knatt, Willia (Box PM5)
    - Landry, Agnes (Box PM5)
    - LeDee, Mary (Box PM5)
    - Livingston, Alice (Box PM5)
    - Manuel, Armstong (Box PM5)
    - Manuel, Beulah (Box PM5)
    - Mathews, Irene (Box PM5)
    - Metz, Ernest (Box PM5)
    - Miller, Sylvania (Box PM5)
    - Miller, Taylor (Box PM5)
    - Mitchell, Maizel (Box PM5)
    - Moore, Albert, Sr. (Box PM5)
    - Noah, Esther (Box PM5)
    - Noah, Joseph (Box PM5)
    - Polk, Edith (Box PM5)
    - Polk, Matthew (Box PM5)
    - Polk, Washington (Box PM5)
    - Raggette, Alfred (Box PM5)
    - Raymond, Albert (Box PM5)
    - Rochelle, Wendy (Box PM5)
    - Russell, James, Sr. (Box PM5)
    - Sigue, Altemus, Jr. (Box PM5)
    - Smith, Alfred (Box PM5)
    - Sutton, Vrginia (Box PM5)
    - Thompson, William, Jr. (Box PM5)
    - Thompson, Joe, Sr. (Box PM5)
    - Vital, Otto (Box PM5)
    - Volter, John (Box PM5)
    - Volter, Victoria (Box PM5)
    - Williams, Grady (Box PM5)
    - Zepherin, William (Box PM5)
  - New Orleans, La. and Environs (Box PM6)
    - Aaron, Dolores (Box PM6)
    - Alexander, Avery (Box PM6)
    - Allen, Philomene (Box PM6)
    - Bartholomew, Norman (Box PM6)
    - Bashful, Emmett (Box PM6)
    - Battiste, Harold (Box PM6)
    - Beslin, Joseph (Box PM6)
    - Borders, Florence (Box PM6)
    - Boucree, John (Box PM6)
    - Bouise, Louise (Box PM6)
    - Brown, Eula (Box PM6)
    - Brumfield, Eddie (Box PM6)
    - Butler, Mary (Box PM6)
    - Caitone, Beverly (Box PM6)
    - Cappie, Herbert (Box PM6)
    - Cappie, Ruth (Box PM6)
    - Charles, Millie (Box PM6)
    - Cheri, Emmett (Box PM6)
    - Clem, Hugh (Box PM6)
    - Cook, Olivia (Box PM6)
    - Dave, Peter, Jr. (Box PM6)
    - Davillier, Brenda (Box PM6)
    - Davis, Mary (Box PM6)
    - Dejan, Harold (Box PM6)
    - Despenza, William (Box PM6)
    - Dunbar, Viola (Box PM6)
    - Elloie, Pealie (Box PM6)
    - Franklin, Louise (Box PM6)
    - Gardner, Albert, Jr. (Box PM6)
    - Goods, Laura (Box PM6)
    - Gourrier, Michael (Box PM6)
    - Hill, Veronica (Box PM6)
    - Honore, Alcee (Box PM6)
    - Hunter, Johnny (Box PM6)
    - Jackson, Olga (Box PM6)
    - Jenkins, Julius (Box PM6)
    - Johnson, Mary (Box PM6)
    - Jordan, Edward (Box PM6)
    - Joseph, Irvin (Box PM6)
    - Kerry, Augusta (Box PM6)
    - Ledoux, Jerome (Box PM6)
    - Lee, Silas (Box PM6)
    - Lundy, Veora (Box PM6)
    - Lyons, Alma (Box PM6)
    - Lyons, Marcus (Box PM6)
    - Macdonald, Bessie (Box PM6)
    - Merrick, Olga (Box PM6)
    - Moore, Hazel (Box PM6)
    - Morial, Francis (Box PM6)
    - Morris, Jeff, Jr. (Box PM6)
    - Mouton, Jessie (Box PM6)
    - Oselen, Maude (Box PM6)
    - Pajeaud, Marjorie (Box PM6)
    - Parker, Quillie (Box PM6)
    - Perry, Lillian (Box PM6)
    - Preston, Mary (Box PM6)
    - Prevost, Maurice (Box PM6)
    - Quant, Brenda (Box PM6)
    - Reed, Clarita (Box PM6)
    - Rhone, Archie (Box PM6)
    - Robertson, Audrey (Box PM6)
    - Robertson, Dolores (Box PM6)
    - Robinson, Wilde (Box PM6)
    - Rousseve, Evelyn (Box PM6)
    - Rousseve, Mildred (Box PM6)
    - Smith, Charles (Box PM6)
    - Smith, Germaine (Box PM6)
    - Smith, Helen (Box PM6)
    - Spencer, Emanuella (Box PM6)
    - St. Julien, Aline (Box PM6)
    - Stanley, Beatrice (Box PM6)
    - Thomas, George, Jr. (Box PM6)
    - Williams, Everett (Box PM6)
  - Norfolk, Va. and Environs
    - Abbyss, Mary (Box PM6)
    - Bass, Lena (Box PM6)
    - Bell, Barbera (Box PM6)
    - Benton, Annie (Box PM6)
    - Boone, Geraldine (Box PM6)
    - Bradley, Dolores (Box PM6)
    - Branchcomb, Flossie (Box PM6)
    - Brandon, Elroy (Box PM6)
    - Brickers, Alease (Box PM6)
    - Brown, John (Box PM6)
    - Brown, Shirley (Box PM6)
    - Cherry, Olivia (Box PM6)
    - Clay, Carnell (Box PM6)
    - Coker, William (Box PM6)
    - Crudup, Henrietta (Box PM6)
    - Dabney, Lena (Box PM6)
    - Downing, Horace (Box PM6)
    - Dozier, Essie (Box PM6)
    - Edmonds, Marian (Box PM6)
    - Edwards, Pearly (Box PM6)
    - Forrest, Kate (Box PM6)
    - Foster, John (Box PM6)
    - Gordon, Margaret (Box PM6)
    - Goss, Jocelyn (Box PM6)
    - Gowens, Madeline (Box PM6)
    - Gray, Cecille (Box PM6)
    - Grimstead, Lucille (Box PM6)
    - Grimstead, Sarah (Box PM6)
    - Hall, Doris (Box PM6)
    - Hayslette, Elnora (Box PM6)
    - Johnson, Harvey (Box PM6)
    - Johnson, Jessie (Box PM6)
    - Lawson, Arthur (Box PM6)
    - Lawson, Leon (Box PM6)
    - Linyear, Josephine (Box PM6)
    - Linyear, William (Box PM6)
    - Littlejohn, Toledo (Box PM6)
    - Lloyd, Esther (Box PM6)
    - Mitchell, Alma (Box PM6)
    - Morgan, Donald (Box PM6)
    - Neal, Andrew (Box PM6)
    - Neal, Velma (Box PM6)
    - Owens, Catherine (Box PM6)
    - Owens, Eugene (Box PM6)
    - Parrish, Doris (Box PM6)
    - Peevy, Evelyn (Box PM6)
    - Perry, Jean (Box PM6)
    - Pharr, Naomi (Box PM6)
    - Phillips, Hazel (Box PM6)
    - Phillips, Jesse (Box PM6)
    - Phillips, Jesse (Box PM6)
    - Porter, Celestine (Box PM6)
    - Rattley, Jessie (Box PM6)
    - Riddick, Mozelle (Box PM6)
    - Riddick, Paul (Box PM6)
    - Rodgers, Alberta (Box PM6)
    - Ryder, Georgia (Box PM6)
    - Sharp, Clarice (Box PM6)
    - Skyles, Walter (Box PM6)
    - Stith, Leah (Box PM6)
    - Studivant, Lenora (Box PM6)
    - Wallace, Jeanette (Box PM6)
    - Watson, William (Box PM6)
    - Wells, Cassie (Box PM6)
    - White, Addie (Box PM6)
    - White, Patricia (Box PM6)
    - Williams, Elwood (Box PM6)
    - Williams, Hortense (Box PM6)
    - Wyatt, George (Box PM6)
  - Orangeburg, S.C. and Environs (Box PM7)
    - Adams, Benjamin (Box PM7)
    - Adams, Fannie (Box PM7)
    - Bonds, Solomon, Jr. (Box PM7)
    - Briggman, Theodue (Box PM7)
    - Brooks, Charles, Sr. (Box PM7)
    - Brunson, John (Box PM7)
    - Caldwell, Rossie (Box PM7)
    - Dawson, Gracia (Box PM7)
    - Felder, Julius (Box PM7)
    - Finney, Ernest, Jr. (Box PM7)
    - Gilbert, Amy (Box PM7)
    - Gore, Blinzy (Box PM7)
    - Harp, Matie (Box PM7)
    - Harper, II, John (Box PM7)
    - Hassell, Betty (Box PM7)
    - Henderson, Ernest (Box PM7)
    - Henderson, Ophelia (Box PM7)
    - Hubbard, Robert (Box PM7)
    - Jamison, Annie (Box PM7)
    - Jamison, Marion, Jr. (Box PM7)
    - Jenkins, Barbara (Box PM7)
    - Kerford, Leo (Box PM7)
    - Lewis, Mary (Box PM7)
    - Lott, Sudie (Box PM7)
    - Martin, II, Frank (Box PM7)
    - Martin, Hattie (Box PM7)
    - McCollom, Irene (Box PM7)
    - McCollom, James (Box PM7)
    - Middleton, Bernice (Box PM7)
    - Middleton, Earl (Box PM7)
    - Mitchell, L. (Box PM7)
    - Mitchell, Rachel (Box PM7)
    - Montgomery, Eugene (Box PM7)
    - Pendergrass, Norman, Sr. (Box PM7)
    - Poole, Larence (Box PM7)
    - Richburg, Joseph (Box PM7)